rocketdock.com 2016-11-11

# Privacy Policy - RocketDock.com

At Punk Labs LLC, we take your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy will define what "personal information" and "non personal information" we collect from RocketDock and RocketDock.com, and how that information is used.

## Personal Information

"Personal Information" is any information that identifies you as an individual. We may collect your name and email address when you register on one of our websites. If you contact us directly for any reason, we may keep a copy of that correspondence.

## Sensitive Information

Sensitive information is defined in the US Privacy Act (1974) to include information or opinion about such things as an individual’s racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, membership of a political association, religious or philosophical beliefs, membership of a professional body, criminal records or health information.

We will not attempt to collect any sensitive information.

## Children

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us at contact@punklabs.com. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

## Disclosure

We will not sell, trade, rent or disclose any of the personal information you provide to us without your prior consent, except where required or allowable by law.

## Security

Your Personal Information is stored offsite in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.

## Non-Personal Information

RocketDock.com may use APIs from third parties to collect and log anonymous data including, but not limited to, the type of web browser and device you use, your device’s unique ID and IP address, and information about the way you use RocketDock.com. This information may be used to analyize and improve RocketDock.com.

## Changes

This Privacy Policy may be updated in the future for any reason. The most up-to-date version of this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.
